https://www.dynamism.com/terms-of-use-and-privacy-policy.shtml#privacy-policy

Search
3D PrintersAllBrandsUltimakerFormlabsNexa3DDesktop MetalBigRepEnvisionTecRaise3DBCN3DMakerbotDremelModixRIZELulzbotXYZKodakBundlesClassroomDesktopIndustrialLarge FormatMetalMaterialsAllBrandsAquaSysBASF UltrafuseBCN3DClariantColorfabbDremelDSMDupontKimya By ArmorMakerBotNinjatekPolymakerRaise3DUltimakerVillage PlasticsXSTRANDXYZFilamentABSASABreakawayCleaningCopolymerNylonPEKKPET-GPLAPolycarbonate (PC)Polypropylene (PP)Soluble SupportSpecialtyTough PLATPU/TPEULTEMResinParts & AccessoriesUltimakerFormlabsBCN3DEnvisionTECLulzbotMakerbotRaise3DRizeProductivity Tools3D ScannersTelepresence RobotFilament SplicersFume ExtractorsLaser CuttersSoftware
Sign In
shopping cart
1-800-310-7968
Order by Phone 1-800-711-6277
Search
Search
Search
Home
Terms Of Use
Terms Of Use
Email
Password
Sign In
Forgot Your Password?
Create an Account
Welcome to the Dynamism web site. By using the Dynamism web site YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY ITS CONDITIONS OF USE and PRIVACY POLICY and all disclaimers and terms and conditions that appear elsewhere on the Dynamism web site.
References to Dynamism herein refer to Dynamism Inc. or Dynamism or its affiliates, subsidiaries and designees as deemed appropriate by Dynamism.
Dynamism reserves the right to make changes to the Dynamism web site and its Conditions of Use and Privacy Policy at any time. Each time you use the Dynamism web site, should visit and review the then current Conditions of Use and Privacy Policy that apply to your transactions and use of this site. If you are dissatisfied with the Dynamism web site, its content or Conditions of Use and Privacy Policy, you agree that your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue using the Dynamism web site.
Tampering with the site, misrepresenting the identity of a user, using buying agents or conducting fraudulent activities on the site are prohibited.
Dynamism does not sell or rent your personal information to third parties.
Dynamism Terms of Use
Disclaimers and Limitation of Liability
By using the Dynamism web site, you expressly agree that use of the Dynamism web site is at your sole risk. The Dynamism web site is provided on an "AS IS" and "as available" basis. Neither Dynamism nor its parent company, affiliates, subsidiaries, or designees nor each of their respective officers, directors, employees, agents, third-party content providers, designers, contractors, distributors, merchants, sponsors, licensors or the like (collectively, "Associates") warrant that use of the Dynamism web site will be uninterrupted or error-free. Neither Dynamism nor its Associates warrant the accuracy, integrity or completeness of the content provided on the Dynamism web site or the products or services offered for sale on the Dynamism web site. Dynamism and its Associates specifically disclaim all warranties, whether expressed or implied, including but not limited to warranties of title, merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose. No oral advice or written information given by Dynamism or its Associates shall create a warranty. Some states do not allow the exclusion or limitation of certain warranties, so the above limitation or exclusion may not apply to you.
Under no circumstances shall Dynamism or its Associates be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special or consequential damages that result from your use of or inability to use the Dynamism web site, including but not limited to reliance by you on any information obtained from the Dynamism web site that results in mistakes, omissions, interruptions, deletion or corruption of files, viruses, delays in operation or transmission, or any failure of performance. The foregoing Limitation of Liability shall apply in any action, whether in contract, tort or any other claim, even if an authorized representative of Dynamism has been advised of or should have knowledge of the possibility of such damages. User hereby acknowledges that this paragraph shall apply to all content, merchandise and services available through the Dynamism web site. Some states do not allow the exclusion or limitation of incidental or consequential damages, so the above limitation or exclusion may not apply to you.
Intended for Users Over 13The Dynamism web site is intended for use by individuals 13 years of age or older. The Dynamism web site is not directed to use by children under the age of 13. Users under the age of 13 should get the assistance of a parent or guardian to use this site.
Errors on Our SitePrices and availability of products and services are subject to change without notice. Errors will be corrected where discovered, and Dynamism reserves the right to revoke any stated offer and to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions including after an order has been submitted and whether or not the order has been confirmed and your credit card charged. If your credit card has already been charged for the purchase and your order is cancelled, Dynamism will issue a credit to your credit card account in the amount of the charge. Individual bank policies will dictate when this amount is credited to your account. If you are not fully satisfied with your purchase, you may return it in accordance with Dynamism’s Return Policy.
Order ValidationAfter you place an order using our shopping cart, we will check the information you give us for validity, by verifying your method of payment or shipping address. We reserve the right to reject any order you place with us, and/or to limit quantities on any order, without giving any reason. If we reject your order, we will attempt to notify you using the e-mail address you have given us with the order.Your credit or debit card will normally not be charged if we reject an order, but we will process a refund if the charge has been made against your card.
Order Acceptance/ConfirmationYour receipt of an electronic or other form of order confirmation does not signify our acceptance of your order, nor does it constitute confirmation of our offer to sell. The Dynamism web site reserves the right at any time after receipt of your order to accept or decline your order for any reason.
Order LimitationsWe reserve the right to reject any order you place with us, and/or or to limit quantities on any order, without giving any reason. If we reject your order, we will generally attempt to notify you using the e-mail address you gave us when you placed the order.
Order Limitations/Limited QuantitiesDynamism may, at its own discretion, limit or cancel quantities purchased per person, per household or per order. Dynamism also reserves the right to reject any order you place with us. These restrictions may include orders placed by the same Dynamism web site account, the same credit card, and orders that use the same billing and/or shipping address. In the event we make a change to an order, we will attempt to notify you by contacting the e-mail and/or billing address provided at the time the order was made.
Termination of UseDynamism may, in its sole discretion, terminate your account or your use of the Dynamism web site at anytime. You are personally liable for any orders that you place or charges that you incur prior to termination. Dynamism reserves the right to change, suspend, or discontinue all or any aspects of the Dynamism web site at any time without prior notice.
Dynamism is committed to protecting your personal information. Dynamism does not request personal information from customers via email or telemarketing. If you are contacted via email or by a telemarketer requesting your personal information on behalf of Dynamism, DO NOT RESPOND. These requests are not from Dynamism. If you have questions about Dynamism’s privacy measures, please contact Dynamism.
Dynamism complies with this privacy policy in the collection, use, sharing and security of customer information, and takes great care in safeguarding your personal information and in complying with all applicable federal and state privacy laws and our own internal standards and best practices. Dynamism is committed to protecting your personal information. Dynamism does not request personal information from customers via email or telemarketing. If you are contacted via email or by a telemarketer requesting your personal information on behalf of Dynamism, DO NOT RESPOND. These requests are not from Dynamism. If you have questions about Dynamism’s privacy measures, please contact sales@dynamism.com.
Dynamism complies with this privacy policy in the collection, use, sharing and security of customer information, and takes great care in safeguarding your personal information and in complying with all applicable federal and state privacy laws and our own internal standards and best practices.
Prefer to call us?1-800-711-6277
Why Dynamism?
We're dedicated to earning each customer's loyalty through exceptional service.
Who We Are
We were founded in 1997. We have offices in Chicago and Denver with four showrooms across the U.S.
Our Company
The leading national supplier of Desktop 3D printers. Expertise in both Industrial and Desktop 3D printing. Supplier of next-generation Metal, SLS, ultrafast Industrial printers.
Customer Benefits
Unlimited toll-free support
Curated selection
Fast shipping
2021 EDITION
Professional 3D Printer Buyers Guide
Choosing the right 3D printer doesn't have to be difficult. Find the perfect printer for your application. This in-depth guide covers pricing, materials, dimensional accuracy, and more.
Download Now
